这种记忆再巩固的理论不仅
Not only does this reconsolidation view
能让我们解释有关记忆的一些古怪之处，
allow us to account for some of the quirks of memory,
比如我们有时都会记错过去的事情，
like how we all sometimes misremember the past,
它还给我们提供了一个方法， 来消除掉导致创伤后应激障碍的
it also gives us a way to destroy those maladaptive fear memories
适应不良的恐惧记忆。
that underlie PTSD.
我们只需要两样东西：
All we would need would be two things:
一个使记忆不稳定的方法—— 也就是用 “编辑” 模式打开文档——
a way of making the memory unstable -- opening that file in edit mode --
以及一个删除信息的途径。
and a way to delete the information.
在研究如何删除信息方面，
We've made the most progress
我们已经取得了很大的进展。
with working out how to delete the information.